ERRON JOHN LAPAC

Email: lapacerronjohn@gmail.com Phone Number: +1 (236) 818-8134 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/erron-john-lapac-7b303727b/

Address: 1235 Astra Pl., Victoria, BC, V8P 5N5

PROFILE SUMMARY

Information technology graduate specializing in web development with expertise in **Bootstrap** and **Laravel**. Possessing strong problem-solving and analytical skills, along with experience in various IT disciplines and related technologies. Ready to contribute knowledge and drive to deliver exceptional results in any IT role.

EDUCATION

COURSERA, California, United States of America

June 2023 – July 2023

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate and React Native (Online)

Professional-level Training and Employer-recognized Certificate from Meta

HOLY NAME UNIVERSITY, Tagbilaran City, Bohol, Philippines **Bachelor in Information Technology**

June 2019 - May 2023

- Dean's Lister
- Commission on Higher Education Scholar
- Government Service Insurance System Scholar

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Frameworks and Library: React, Laravel, and Bootstrap
- Programming Languages: Javascript, PHP, HTML 5, CSS
- Microsoft Office: Excel, Word and PowerPoint
- Database Designs: Laragon, Xampp, VitualBox and Postman
- Valuable Applications: OBS Studio, Source Tree, Github, Figma, Cypress
- Photo and Video Editing: Adobe Photoshop, Canva and VSDC Video Editor
- Others: Microsoft Visual Studio, Google Drive, Node.js, Composer, Jira and Bitbucket

WORK EXPERIENCE

GLOBALOR PHILIPPINES, Bohol, Philippines

May 2022 - May 2023

UI/UX Designer Intern

- Created user-centered designs by understanding business requirements, and user feedback.
- Generated user flows, wireframes, prototypes and mockups and translated requirements into style guides, design systems, design patterns and attractive user interfaces.
 - UX Planning and Designing

Prototyping

UI Design and Validation

- UI / UX Evaluation
- Gather User Feedback
- Message Content

Front-End Developer Intern

- Applied the knowledge of programming languages to code user-side applications, including visual elements like menu bars, clickable buttons and the overall layout of websites or web applications.
 - Design Implementation
 - UI Design and Evaluation
 - o API Integration

- Technical Recommendation
- Code Documentation
- Code Organization

Back-End Developer Intern

- Handled the development and maintenance of server-side components and gained practical and theoretical experience that can be applied to real-life scenarios.
- Contributed to tasks such as coding, troubleshooting, and collaborating with the front-end team.
 - O Developed Back-End Functionalities

Managed Database and Server

Developed API

O Code and API Documentation

Quality Assurance Intern (Automation/Manual)

- Spearheaded the product quality, testing each part to ensure it meets company standards before moving to the next phase.
- Developed tools that will improve the testing process and provided improvement feedback to the Project Manager.
 - Test Applications (Web & Mobile Application)
 - Manual testing
 - Automation scripting

- Issue tracking and bug reporting
- o Technical recommendation
- Code organization
- Code documentation

UPWORK GLOBAL INC., California, United States of America

June 2020 - PRESENT

Virtual Assistant Freelancer

- Conducted research and gathered data on specific customer segments for lead generation purposes and utilized various sources and tools to collect information.
- Identified target customer profiles based on specified criteria and parameters as well as verified and validated lead information to ensure accuracy and reliability.
- Managed, updated and organized lead databases to track progress and measure effectiveness, and provided regular reports and updates to stakeholders.

JJS DATA MINING, Bohol, Philippines

June 2016 - August 2016

Lead Generation Assistant

- Proficient in providing virtual assistant services, specializing in lead generation and social media.
- Experienced in researching and identifying potential leads within target markets.
- Strong attention to detail in maintaining accurate lead databases and tracking lead interactions.

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Proficiency in coding
- Collaboration skills
- Fast learner

- Problem-solving abilities
- Attention to detail
- Analytical thinking

REFERENCES

CHARLIEMAGNE I. CLAROS
Project Manager / Senior Mobile Developer
GlobalOR Philippines
Charliemagneclaros08@gmail.com

DR. MARIA CELIA Z. LIGASON Chairperson, Computer Studies Holy Name University cs.chair.coecs@hnu.edu.ph

ENGR. JAMES P. UY
Dean, College of Engineering & Computer Studies
Holy Name University
coecs.dean@hnu.edu.ph